Sol M. Linowitz Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- General Office File, 1778-1999 (Box 136-538)
  - Part A, 1778-1967 (Box 136-291)
    - United Nations
      - United Nations Conference on the Application of Science and Technology for the Benefit of the Less Developed Areas, Geneva
        - Correspondence, 1962-1963, undated, (4 folders)
        - Miscellany
          - 1957-1963, Mar., (3 folders)
          - 1963, Apr., undated, (3 folders) (Box 290)
      - United States delegation, 1955-1962, undated, (3 folders)
    - United States Army, 1964
    - United States Atomic Energy Commission, 1954-1957
    - Utica Aviation School
      - Charts, 1943
      - Correspondence, 1943
      - Hanger storage, 1943
      - Miscellany, 1943-1944, 1952, undated, (2 folders)
      - Reports, 1943
    - Vanden Heuvel, William J., 1962-1965 (Box 291)
    - Wills, 1948, 1958-1964, undated
    - Wollensak Optical Co., 1958
    - World Brotherhood Community Award, 1957-1961, undated, (2 folders)
    - Zipser, Alfred R., 1965-1966
  - Part B, 1948-1999 (Box 291-538)
    Correspondence sent and received, speeches and writings, organizational records, legal files, reports, notes, telephone logs, travel files, photographs, clippings, and printed matter representing most of Linowitz's career after leaving the Organization of American States in 1969.
    - Academy for Educational Development (Box 291)
      - Board of Directors meetings, 1977, 1988-1991, (4 folders)
      - Correspondence (Box 292)
        - 1978-1990, (9 folders)
        - 1991-1992, (2 folders) (Box 293)
      - Speech by Linowitz, 1991
    - Action for Legal Rights, 1971
    - Adlai Stevenson Institute of International Affairs, 1966-1970, undated, (5 folders)
    - Air Force Academy Foundation, 1975 (Box 294)
    - Albert Einstein Memorial, Advisory Committee, Washington, D.C., 1978-1979, undated
    - Alfalfa Club, Washington, D.C., 1981-1999, (2 folders)
    - Alliance to Save Energy, 1977-1982
    - America-Israel Cultural Foundation, 1970-1971
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences
      - Assembly on University Goals and Governance, Boston, Mass., 1968-1971, (2 folders)
      - Correspondence
        - 1971-1978, 1987, (2 folders)
        - 1988-1992, (6 folders) (Box 295)
      - Dinner, 1990, May 16
      - Public Affairs Membership Committee, 1988-1990
    - American Academy of Diplomacy (Box 296)
      - Board of Directors meetings
        - 1985-1989, (8 folders)
        - 1990-1991, (2 folders) (Box 297)
      - Diplomatic Award
        - 1987
        - 1989
      - Ford Foundation, 1985-1988, (2 folders)
      - General correspondence
        - 1983, Apr.-1984, Apr., (3 folders)
        - 1984, May-1986, July, (12 folders) (Box 298)
        - 1986, Aug.-1991, Dec., (14 folders) (Box 299)
        - 1992, Jan.-1993, Jan., (4 folders) (Box 300)
      - Membership, 1986-1989, undated
      - Miscellany, 1980-1989, undated, (2 folders)
      - Newsom, David D., 1985-1988, (3 folders)
      - Popper, David H., 1988-1989, (2 folders) (Box 301)
      - Reports, 1987-1988
      - Seminars, 1988
      - Una Chapman Cox Foundation, 1986-1989, undated, (2 folders)
      - United States Congress, 1987-1988
    - American Assembly
      - 1966, Nov.-1969, Nov., (2 folders)
      - 1970, Feb.-1988, Feb., (11 folders) (Box 302)
      - 1988, Mar.-1992, Apr., (11 folders) (Box 303)
      - 1992, May-Dec., undated, (2 folders) (Box 304)
    - American Bar Association
      - Commission on Law and the Economy, 1976-1977
      - International Human Rights Trial Observer Project, 1988
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1986
      - Standing Committee on Federal Judiciary, 1970-1971, undated
    - American Council on Education, 1987
    - American Field Service, 1966-1970, (5 folders)
    - American Jewish Committee (Box 305)
      - Ad Hoc Committee
        - Correspondence, 1986-1989, (8 folders)
        - Form letters, 1986-1987
        - Meetings
          - 1986, (3 folders)
          - 1987-1991, (7 folders) (Box 306)
        - Miscellany, 1990-1991
      - Board of Governors, minutes of meetings, 1969-1970
      - Correspondence, 1967-1991, (8 folders) (Box 307)
      - Position statements, 1967-1970
      - Speeches by Linowitz, 1965, undated
    - American Jewish Congress (Box 308)
      - Advisory Committee, a policy study of the Arab-Israel conflict
        - Correspondence, 1988-1989, undated, (2 folders)
        - Report, 1988
      - Miscellany, 1985-1991
    - American Red Cross
      - Endowment Fund, 1979, (4 folders)
      - Correspondence See also Oversize
        - 1970, Feb.-1972, Jan., (3 folders)
        - 1972, Feb.-1982, May, undated, (5 folders) (Box 309)
      - Magen David Adom New Agenda Advisory Committee, 1988-1990, (3 folders)
    - American Women's Economic Development Corp., 1989-1990, undated
    - Americares Foundation, 1986-1991
    - Americas Society (Box 310)
      - Commission on Western Hemisphere Foreign Debt and Public Policy, 1983-1984, (3 folders)
      - Correspondence, 1987-1992, (8 folders)
    - Aspen Institute, 1978-1982, undated, (4 folders) (Box 311)
    - Atlantic Council of the United States
      - Correspondence
        - 1981-1988, (6 folders)
        - 1989-1991, (8 folders) (Box 312)
      - Program Committee, 1988-1989
    - Bicentennial Conference on the Constitution, Philadelphia, Pa., 1976, Apr. 5-8
    - Bohemian Club, San Francisco, Calif.
      - Correspondence and notes
        - 1972
        - 1976-1990 (Box 313)
      - Miscellany, 1971-1990, undated See also Oversize, (4 folders)
    - Bolivarian Society of the United States, 1968-1969, undated
    - Bordan, Inc., Ad Hoc Steering Group, 1970-1971
    - Bretton Woods Committee, 1987-1990, (4 folders)
    - Brookings Institution, Washington, D.C., 1969, 1975-1977
    - Brown University, Providence, R.I., 1973
    - Business Enterprise Trust (Box 314)
      - Awards
        - 1991
          - Candidates
          - Finalists
          - Presentation ceremonies
        - 1992
          - Candidates
          - Finalists
          - Presentation ceremonies
        - 1993 (Box 315)
          - Candidates
          - Finalists
      - Board of Trustees meetings, 1989-1991, (6 folders)
      - Business Responsibility Research Partnership, 1992
      - Correspondence
        - 1989, (2 folders)
        - 1990-1992, (9 folders) (Box 316)
      - Proposal to Alfred P. Sloan Foundation, 1992
    - Business International Corp.
      - Board of Directors meetings
        - 1977
        - 1978-1979, (6 folders) (Box 317)
      - Chief Executive Officers Roundtable
        - 1971-1973, (2 folders)
        - 1978-1979, (4 folders) (Box 318)
      - Correspondence
        - 1970-1975, (5 folders)
        - 1976-1983, (7 folders) (Box 319)
    - Carter Center, Emory University, Atlanta, Ga.
      - Correspondence, 1987-1992, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1986-1989
      - New Hemispheric Agenda conference, Atlanta, Ga., 1989
    - Center for Excellence in Government, 1987-1988 (Box 320)
    - Center for Inter-American Relations, 1971-1980, undated, (6 folders)
    - Center for Public Resources, 1981-1991, (5 folders)
    - Center for Strategic and International Studies, 1986-1989 (Box 321)
    - Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, 1978-1979
    - Century Association, New York, N.Y., 1969-1999, (3 folders)
    - Chancellor's Panel on University Purposes, State University of New York, Albany, N.Y., 1971
    - Chautauqua Institution, Chautauqua, N.Y., 1987-1991
    - China, 1978-1979
    - Citizens' Committee on Population and the American Future, 1972-1973
    - Citizens' Committee for the Bicentennial, 1973
    - Citizens for Justice with Order, 1969-1970
    - Citizens Network for Foreign Affairs
      - Background and action plan, 1986-1987, undated
      - Bylaws, 1987
      - Correspondence (Box 322)
        - 1987-1991, (12 folders)
        - 1992-1993, (5 folders) (Box 323)
      - Meetings
        - 1987, June-1989, Jan., (5 folders)
        - 1989, Dec.-1993, Sept., (6 folders) (Box 324)
      - Miscellany, 1987
    - Claremont Graduate School, Claremont, Calif.
      - 1986
      - 1987-1990, (4 folders) (Box 325)
    - Clark College, Atlanta, Ga., 1971-1972
    - Club of Rome, Italy, 1973-1992, undated, (5 folders)
    - Coalition for Adequate Judicial Compensation, 1975-1977, undated
    - Columbia University, New York, N.Y.
      - Advisory Council of the School of International Affairs, 1969-1973
      - Columbia Journal of World Business, 1971-1972
      - Correspondence, 1976-1977
    - Commerce Department, Secretary's Advisory Council, 1976-1977 (Box 326)
    - Commission on Critical Choices for Americans
      - Correspondence, 1973-1976, undated, (4 folders)
      - Reports, 1951, 1972-1975, (5 folders)
    - Commission on United States-Latin American Relations (Box 327)
      - Congressional hearings, 1974
      - Correspondence
        - 1973, Oct.-1975, June, (15 folders)
        - 1975, July-1977, Mar., (11 folders) (Box 328)
      - Foreword by Linowitz for New Horizons for the Third World by Francisco Casanova Alvarez
      - Meetings
        - Agendas, 1974
        - Minutes, 1974, (2 folders) (Box 329)
      - Miscellany, 1971-1974, undated, (3 folders)
      - Position papers
        - Arms policy, 1974, undated
        - Brazil, 1974, undated
        - Caribbean policy, 1974, undated
        - Cuba, 1974-1976, undated
        - Economic policy
          - 1973-1974
          - 1976, undated (Box 330)
        - Human rights, 1970-1974
        - Inter-American system, 1969-1974, undated
        - Law of the sea, 1973-1974, undated
        - Miscellany, 1974, undated
        - Panama, 1974, undated
      - Press coverage, 1974, undated
      - Reports (Box 331)
        - Drafting Committee, 1974, undated
        - Drafts, 1974, undated, (3 folders)
        - Final versions, 1974-1976
    - Commission to Study the Organization of Peace, 1971-1974
    - Congressional Board of the Office of Technology Assessments, Advisory Panel on Applications of Science and Technology, 1976-1978
    - Consortium of Universities, Washington, D.C., 1967-1973, (3 folders)
    - Cornell Law School, Ithaca, N.Y. (Box 332)
      - Correspondence, 1978-1993, (10 folders)
      - Speech by Linowitz
        - Correspondence, 1988-1992
          - A-C, (3 folders)
          - D-Z, (11 folders) (Box 333)
        - Drafts
          - 1987
          - 1988, (3 folders) (Box 334)
        - Excerpts, 1988
        - Final versions, 1988
        - Miscellany, 1981-1988, undated
        - Press coverage, 1988-1990, undated, (2 folders)
        - Reading copies, 1988
        - Resource materials, 1981-1992, undated, (2 folders)
    - Cornell University, Ithaca, N.Y. (Box 335)
      - Academic Affairs Committee, 1977-1979, 1990-1991, (4 folders)
      - Board of Trustees meetings
        - 1979, (2 folders)
        - 1987, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 336)
        - 1987-1988, (1 vol.)
        - 1988, (2 folders)
        - 1989, Jan., (2 folders)
        - 1989, Mar.-1990, May, (8 folders) (Box 337)
        - 1990, June-1992, May, (10 folders) (Box 338)
        - 1992, Oct.-1993, Oct., (9 folders) (Box 339)
      - Commission on Minority Participation in Education and American Life, 1987-1988, undated, (3 folders) (Box 340)
      - Committee on Board Membership
        - Annual agenda outlines, 1989-1994, (5 folders)
        - Correspondence
          - 1986-1988, (2 folders)
          - 1989-1993, (4 folders) (Box 341)
        - Meetings
          - 1989, Dec.-1990, Dec., (9 folders)
          - 1991, Jan.-1993, Mar., (10 folders) (Box 342)
          - 1993, Apr.-Nov., (3 folders) (Box 343)
      - Eastern Europe Seminar, 1990, undated
      - Executive Committee meetings, 1986-1989, (5 folders)
      - General correspondence
        - 1968-1969, (3 folders)
        - 1970-1980, (12 folders) (Box 344)
        - 1981-1990, (11 folders) (Box 345)
        - 1991-1993, (6 folders) (Box 346)
      - Fund-raising campaign, 1990
      - Institute of Peace Studies and Peace Science, proposed, 1980-1982
      - International Programs Committee, 1990
      - Miscellany, 1985-1990
      - Rhodes, Frank Harold Trevor
        - 1987-1989, (3 folders)
        - 1990-1993, (5 folders) (Box 347)
      - Society for the Humanities, 1981-1984
      - South Africa issues, 1978, 1988-1990
      - University Council, 1987-1993
      - World Center, proposed, 1988
    - Cosmos Club, Washington, D.C., 1998
    - Coudert Brothers
      - Billing actions, 1992
        - Business development
        - Monthly, 1992
          - Jan.-Apr.
          - May-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 348)
        - Pro bono
      - Offices
        - Beijing, China, 1982, undated
        - Hong Kong, 1982, undated
        - Moscow, USSR
          - Press coverage, 1984-1988, (4 folders)
          - Sitrick, James B., 1987-1988, (3 folders) (Box 349)
          - Torem, Charles
            - 1987, Apr.-1988, July, (9 folders)
            - 1988, Aug.-Dec. (Box 350)
        - New York, N.Y.
          - General correspondence, 1981-1988, (9 folders)
          - Hoffman, Elinor R.,1987-1988, undated, (3 folders)
          - Miscellany, 1970, 1986-1988
          - Sitrick, James B., 1986-1988, (3 folders)
        - Paris, France, 1970, 1987-1988, (4 folders) (Box 351)
        - San Francisco, Calif., 1976-1979
        - Singapore, 1979-1982
        - Sydney, Australia, 1987-1988, (3 folders)
        - Tokyo, Japan
          - General correspondence, 1978-1982, undated
          - Visa problems, 1979, (4 folders)
        - Washington, D.C., 1987-1992, (7 folders) (Box 352)
    - Council of American Ambassadors, 1984-1990, (7 folders)
    - Council of the Americas, 1968-1976, undated, (5 folders) (Box 353)
    - Council on Foreign Relations
      - Correspondence
        - 1966-1987, (7 folders)
        - 1988-1993, (9 folders) (Box 354)
      - Current Issue Review Group on Cuba, 1972-1975, (4 folders)
    - Democratic National Committee, Foreign Affairs Task Force, 1974-1976, (3 folders) (Box 355)
    - Earl Warren Legal Training Program, National Lawyers Advisory Council, 1971-1972, undated
    - Economic Club of Washington, D.C., 1986-1993, (5 folders)
    - Education and World Affairs, 1969-1970
    - Eisenhower Seminar, Washington, D.C., 1978-1993, (3 folders)
    - Energy Mobilization Board, proposal, 1979 (Box 356)
    - Federal City Council, Washington, D.C.
      - Background materials for projects, fiscal year 1974, (5 folders)
      - Bylaws, 1971
      - Correspondence
        - 1974, July-1976, July, (5 folders)
        - 1976, Aug.-1988, Sept., (12 folders) (Box 357)
        - 1988, Oct.-1993, Nov., (10 folders) (Box 358)
      - Metro Task Force, 1977 (Box 359)
      - Speeches by Linowitz, 1974-1978
    - Federal Judicial Center, Washington, D.C., 1986-1987
    - Folger Shakespeare Library, Washington, D.C., 1986-1988
    - Foreign Policy Association
      - 1969-1977, (9 folders)
      - 1978-1979, (2 folders) (Box 360)
    - Foundation for International Technological Cooperation, 1978-1979, undated
    - Hamilton College, Clinton, N.Y.
      - Board of Trustees
        - Correspondence, 1987-1990, (8 folders)
        - Meetings
          - 1969-1979, (2 folders); (9 folders) (Box 361)
          - 1987, Mar., (3 folders)
          - 1987, June-1988, Mar., (7 folders) (Box 362)
          - 1988, June-1989, Sept., (10 folders) (Box 363)
          - 1989, Dec.-1991, Mar., (13 folders) (Box 364)
          - 1991, May-1992, Sept., (12 folders) (Box 365)
          - 1992, Dec., (2 folders) (Box 366)
      - Class reunion, 1990
      - Committee on Honorary Degrees, 1970-1978, undated, (4 folders)
      - Correspondence
        - 1966, Nov.-1968, Sept., (4 folders)
        - 1968, Oct.-1978, July, (14 folders) (Box 367)
        - 1978, Aug.-1992, Jan., (14 folders) (Box 368)
    - Harris, Beach and Wilcox, Rochester, N.Y., 1966-1981, (6 folders) (Box 369)
    - Harvard University, Cambridge, Mass.
      - Center for International Affairs, 1973-1979, 1989-1992, (4 folders)
      - Harvard Business Review, article by Ralph Diaz and Linowitz
        - Correspondence, 1969-1973, (3 folders)
        - Text, 1972
      - John F. Kennedy School of Government
        - Public Policy and Corporate Management Program, 1982-1984, (2 folders)
        - Visiting Committee, 1970-1991, undated, (6 folders) (Box 370)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1989-1992
      - World Food Policy Seminar, 1979, (3 folders)
    - Hastings Center, Hastings-on-Hudson, N.Y., 1981-1982
    - Institute for Politics and Planning, 1969-1971
    - Institute for Scientific and Technological Cooperation, 1980
    - Institute for World Order (Box 371)
      - Correspondence, 1973-1974
      - Reports, 1972-1974, undated, (4 folders)
    - Institute for International Education, 1966-1978, (5 folders)
    - Inter-American Dialogue
      - Annual report, 1987
      - Aspen Institute, 1987-1988, (2 folders) (Box 372)
      - Clippings, 1985-1986, (2 folders)
      - Congressional testimony, 1983-1985, undated, (3 folders)
      - Contadora Group, 1983-1984
      - Executive Committee
        - Meetings
          - 1989-1990, (2 folders)
          - 1991-1992, (6 folders) (Box 373)
        - Miscellany
          - 1982-1990, (3 folders)
          - 1991 (Box 374)
      - First Summit of Western Hemisphere Ministers of Finance, Washington, D.C., 1992
      - Foundations, 1990-1991, (2 folders)
      - General correspondence
        - 1982-1983
          - A-Pe, (8 folders)
          - Pf-Z, (2 folders) (Box 375)
        - 1984, A-W, (8 folders)
        - 1985
          - A-La, (4 folders)
          - Lo-W, (6 folders) (Box 376)
        - 1986, B-W, (4 folders)
        - 1987
          - A-K, (4 folders)
          - L-Z, (3 folders) (Box 377)
        - 1988, A-W, (8 folders)
        - 1989
          - A-G, (3 folders)
          - H-Z, (5 folders) (Box 378)
        - 1990
          - A-K, (10 folders)
          - L-Y, (7 folders) (Box 379)
        - 1991, A-W, (5 folders)
        - 1992
          - A-J, (2 folders)
          - M-W, (2 folders) (Box 380)
      - Membership, 1989-1991, undated, (4 folders)
      - North American Free Trade Agreement, 1990-1991, (2 folders)
      - Officers and staff
        - Bell, Peter D.
          - 1987, Aug.-1991, Oct., (5 folders)
          - 1991, Nov.-1992, (2 folders) (Box 381)
        - Feinberg, Richard E., 1992-1993, (5 folders)
        - Hakim, Peter
          - 1986, Nov.-1989, Apr., (8 folders)
          - 1989, May-1992, Mar., (12 folders) (Box 382)
          - 1992, Apr.-Nov., (4 folders) (Box 383)
        - Johnson, Victor C., 1987
        - Lowenthal, Abraham F.
          - 1982, Oct.-1987, Mar., (9 folders)
          - 1987, Apr.-1990, Apr., (13 folders) (Box 384)
          - 1990, May-1992, May, (15 folders) (Box 385)
          - 1992, June-1993, Jan., undated, (3 folders) (Box 386)
        - Plaza Lasso, Galo, 1987
        - Pyatt, Geoffrey, 1989, (2 folders)
      - Panama trip, 1991, (3 folders)
      - Photographs, 1983, undated
      - Plenary sessions
        - 1985, Nov., (3 folders)
        - 1987, Oct., (1 folder); (6 folders) (Box 387)
        - 1988, Nov.-1990, July, (5 folders)
        - 1992, Apr., (3 folders) (Box 388)
      - Press coverage, 1984-1990, (7 folders)
      - Reports
        - Drafts
          - 1988, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box 389)
          - 1989, (6 folders)
          - 1990, (3 folders) (Box 390)
        - Printed copies and related material, 1983-1989, (3 folders)
      - Sol M. Linowitz Forum
        - Correspondence, 1996-1997
        - Photographs, 1996
      - Speeches and writings (Box 391)
        - Articles by members and staff
          - Set I, 1986-1987
          - Set II, 1984-1989, undated, (5 folders)
        - Articles by or for Linowitz
          - “Daggers of Debt, Drugs Aiming at the Americas,” 1988, (2 folders)
          - “Facing Up to Nicaragua,” 1986-1987
          - “For a Bipartisan Policy on Nicaragua,” 1987
          - “Latin America - the President's Agenda,” 1988-1989, (1 folder); (5 folders) (Box 392)
          - Miscellaneous, 1984-1989, undated, (3 folders)
        - Speeches by or for Linowitz
          - Americas Foundation speech, 1985
          - “Countdown in U.S.-Latin America Relations,” 1988, (1 folder) (Box 393)
          - Miscellaneous, 1984-1987, undated, (3 folders)
          - “Moment of Truth in U.S.-Latin America Relations,” 1989, (3 folders)
      - Working file
        - Argentina, 1987
        - Brazil
          - 1982, Dec.-1987, Mar., (2 folders)
          - 1987, Apr.-1991, Nov., (4 folders) (Box 394)
        - Central America
          - 1983, Sept.-1985, Nov., (8 folders)
          - 1986, Jan.-1987, Sept., (10 folders) (Box 395)
          - 1987, Oct.-1990, Feb., (9 folders) (Box 396)
          - Undated, (1 folder) (Box 397)
        - Chile, 1976-1977, 1987
        - Cuba, 1974, 1992-1993
        - Democracy, 1985, undated
        - Drugs, 1985-1990, undated
        - Latin America
          - 1968, Mar.-1969, Dec., (4 folders)
          - 1970, Jan.-1984, Nov., (9 folders) (Box 398)
          - 1985, May-1989, Oct., (8 folders) (Box 399)
          - 1989, Nov.-1992, Feb., (6 folders) (Box 400)
          - Undated, (4 folders); (1 folder) (Box 401)
        - Latin American debt, 1985-1990, undated, (9 folders)
        - Mexico
          - 1985
          - 1986-1991, (3 folders) (Box 402)
        - Miscellany
          - 1977, Mar.-1986, Aug., (7 folders)
          - 1986, Sept.-1988, Nov., (15 folders) (Box 403)
          - 1988, Dec.-1990, June, (8 folders) (Box 404)
          - 1990, July-1993, Dec., (3 folders) (Box 405)
        - Nicaragua
          - 1983, Dec.-1987, June, (10 folders)
          - 1987, July-1990, July, (3 folders) (Box 406)
        - Panama
          - 1977, June-1988, May, (8 folders)
          - 1988, June-1993, July, (14 folders) (Box 407)
          - 1994, July, undated, (2 folders) (Box 408)
    - Inter-American Foundation, 1987
    - International Center for Economic Growth
      - Board of Overseers, 1990
      - Correspondence, 1987-1992, undated, (4 folders)
    - International Chamber of Commerce, United States Council
      - Correspondence, 1969-1977, (4 folders)
      - Executive Committee
        - 1973
        - 1974, (3 folders) (Box 409)
    - International Commission for Central American Recovery and Development
      - Comments on report, 1987-1989
      - Committees 1-5, 1988, (5 folders)
      - Correspondence
        - 1987-1988, A-W, (5 folders)
        - 1989-1990, A-W, (4 folders) (Box 410)
      - Meetings
        - 1987, Dec., San Jose, Costa Rica
        - 1988, June, Stockholm, Sweden, (4 folders)
        - 1988, Nov., Washington, D.C., (2 folders); (3 folders) (Box 411)
      - Miscellany, 1987-1990, undated, (4 folders)
      - Report, 1988
      - United Nations Development Programme, 1987-1989
    - International Council for Educational Development (Box 412)
      - Board of Trustees meetings, 1974-1978, (2 folders)
      - Correspondence, 1970-1991, (5 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1973-1974
    - International Executive Service Corps
      - Board of Directors meetings
        - 1974, (3 folders)
        - 1987-1992, (2 folders) (Box 413)
      - Breakthrough Program, proposed, 1989
      - Correspondence
        - 1964-1986, (8 folders)
        - 1987-1992, (12 folders) (Box 414)
      - Frank Pace Award Committee (Box 415)
        - 1988
          - Ceremonies
          - Selection process, (2 folders)
        - 1989, selection process
        - 1990
          - Ceremonies
          - Selection process, (2 folders)
      - Pace, Frank, memorial, 1982
      - Printed matter
        - 1974-1978, (2 folders)
        - 1979-1992, (3 folders) (Box 416)